迈克 · 诺斯: 我们这里也有，类似这样的句法。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: We also have here,
something like this syntax here.
所以我一直把类型 perimeter 比作函数参数。
So I've been likening type
perimeters to function arguments.
基于这个类比,
Based on that analogy,
有人能猜一下在这种情况下，什么等于什么吗？
can someone venture a guess as to what
equals any means in this context?
演讲者2: [听不见]迈克 · 诺斯: 那是什么？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: [INAUDIBLE]
&gt;&gt; Mike North: What's that?
演讲者2: 默认值是 any。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Default value is an any.
麦克 · 诺斯: 正确,
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Correct,
如果没有任何类型的警戒线，我们就撤退到任何。
if no type perimeter is provided,
we fall back to an any.
这是此类型参数的默认值。
That is the default of
this type parameter.
所以在这里，如果我们盘旋在这上面,
So here, if we hover over this,
这是一个任意值，这是真值的过滤器。
this ends up being an any and
this is sort of a filter for truth values.
排序通过 x 直接通过，它通过 val 直接通过。
Sort of passes X straight through,
it passes val straight through.
因此，这就是你可以期待的结果。
And, as a result,
this is what you could expect.
你将不会得到类型错误传递一个参数到这里,
You'll get no type errors for
passing an argument to this,
因为任何事情都会发生，对吗？
cause anything goes, right?
所以它等价于一个默认参数值。
So it's the equivalent of
a default parameter value.
它只是一个默认类型。
It's just a default type.
Mike North: 到目前为止，在我们的例子中，比如这个例子,
&gt;&gt; Mike North: So, so far,
in our examples, like in this example,
我们已经声明了这个类型参数 t 和
we've declared that we have
this type parameter, T, and
我们发现我们直接使用 t。
we have found that we're using T directly.
但是你不必总是这样做，你不仅仅局限于此。
But you don't always have to do that,
you're not limited to that.
这里有一个例子，有点复杂，但是
Here's an example,
a little bit more complicated but
我从我自己的代码中抽出来的一个，迈克 · 诺斯: 当传递一个承诺时,
one that I pulled out of my own code that,
&gt;&gt; Mike North: When passed a promise,
这就像承诺类型是泛型的类型，它解析为。
and this is like the promise type is
generic over the type that it resolves to.
当我们说泛型的时候意思就是泛型,
And when we say generic
over that means that it is,
它将解析的类型抽象为，并将其作为类型参数。
it abstracts the type that it resolves to,
it takes it as a type parameter.
所以你可以有一个承诺，解析为一个数字，或者
So you could have a promise
that resolves to a number, or
一个解析为 HTTP 响应的承诺，对吗？
a promise that resolves to
an HTTP response, right?
这就是你呼叫 fetch 时得到的回应。
That's what you get back
when you call fetch.
所以 t 是参数，但我把它作为参数
So T is the parameter, but
I take as an argument Promise T and
我将根据我得到的承诺和它的类型推断出 t 必须是什么。
I'll infer what T must be based on
the promise that I'm given and its type.
它以承诺和论点为基础，以一个数作为论点,
So it takes a promises and argument and
it takes a number as an argument,
它会带回一个新的承诺，如果时间到了就会暂停。
and it'll return a new promise
that'll either time out if time's up.
或者承诺在时间到之前就结束了,
Or if the promise resolves
before it time's up,
它实际上会传递这个承诺的结果值。
it'll actually pass through
the result value of that promise.
这里是实现，应该有意义。
And here is the implementation,
should hopefully make sense.
它叫做 setTimeout。
It's called setTimeout.
为了取消超时，setTimeout 返回的内容是必要的
This thing that setTimeout returns is
necessary in order to cancel the timeout
后来。
later on.
如果没有其他事情发生，这一切都是为了拒绝承诺。
And it's all set up, if nothing else
happens, to reject the promise.
如果承诺解除，我们取消超时。
If the promise resolves,
we cancel the timeout.
还没完成,
It's not finished,
我们传递给 setTimeout 的回调可能永远不会被调用。
the callback that we passed to
setTimeout may never get invoked.
然后我们用值来解析。
And then we resolve with the value.
注意，我不需要传入任何带有尖括号的内容。
Note that I don't have to pass in
anything with angle brackets here.
原因是 fetch 返回一个承诺，解析为一个响应。
And the reason is fetch returns
a promise that resolves to a response.
通过接受这个论点,
And so through receiving this an argument,
类型脚本指出 t 必须是一个响应。
type script figures out
that T must be a response.
它推断出 t 是什么，通过某种程度上从承诺或
It infers what T is by kind of
plucking it out of the promise or
这种承诺。
the type of the promise.